<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software and Tool on Shixiang Wang | 王诗翔</title>
    <link>/en/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software and Tool on Shixiang Wang | 王诗翔</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>UCSCXenaTools: Download Public Cancer Genomic Data from UCSC Xena Hubs</title>
      <link>/en/tools/ucscxenatools-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/tools/ucscxenatools-intro/</guid>
      <description>UCSCXenaTools is an R package for downloading and exploring data from UCSC Xena data hubs, which are
 a collection of UCSC-hosted public databases such as TCGA, ICGC, TARGET, GTEx, CCLE, and others. Databases are normalized so they can be combined, linked, filtered, explored and downloaded.
– UCSC Xena
 If you use this package in academic field, please cite:
Wang, Shixiang, et al. &amp;quot;The predictive power of tumor mutational burden in lung cancer immunotherapy response is influenced by patients&amp;#39; sex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UCSCXenaTools: R API for UCSC Xena Hubs</title>
      <link>/en/tools/ucscxenatools-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/tools/ucscxenatools-api/</guid>
      <description>This vignette gives users the summary information of API functions provided by UCSCXenaTools for UCSC Xena.
Before using API, user should know some concepts about Xena elements. Following description is copied from xenaPython __init__.py.
 Data rows are associated with “sample” IDs.
Sample IDs are unique within a “cohort”. s A “dataset” is a particular assay of a cohort, e.g. gene expression.
Datasets have associated metadata, specifying their data type and cohort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contribution - A Tiny Contribution Table Generator Based on ggplot2</title>
      <link>/en/tools/contribution-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/tools/contribution-table/</guid>
      <description>The goal of contribution is to generate contribution table for credit assignment in a project. This is inspired by Nick Steinmetz (see twitter https://twitter.com/SteinmetzNeuro/status/1147241138291527681). Authors contributions sections are new and still don’t appear in major journals, but can be improved. Rather than text listing each author’s contributions, the same data can be presented as a table with rows corresponding</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>