<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UCSCXenaTools on Shixiang Wang | 王诗翔</title>
    <link>/tags/ucscxenatools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in UCSCXenaTools on Shixiang Wang | 王诗翔</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/ucscxenatools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiplot Xena 镜像与官方网站下载速度测评</title>
      <link>/cn/post/2020-12-14-test-download-speed-with-hiplot-ucsc-xena-mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cn/post/2020-12-14-test-download-speed-with-hiplot-ucsc-xena-mirror/</guid>
      <description>最近剑峰在 Hiplot 服务器上线了 UCSC Xena 的镜像，本文是对已部署镜像的下载速度情况进行一个简单的测评。 数据集选择 使用更新到 1.4.0 的 UCSCXenaTools https://githu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UCSCXenaTools: Download Public Cancer Genomic Data from UCSC Xena Hubs</title>
      <link>/en/tools/ucscxenatools-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/tools/ucscxenatools-intro/</guid>
      <description>UCSCXenaTools is an R package for downloading and exploring data from UCSC Xena data hubs, which are
 a collection of UCSC-hosted public databases such as TCGA, ICGC, TARGET, GTEx, CCLE, and others. Databases are normalized so they can be combined, linked, filtered, explored and downloaded.
– UCSC Xena
 If you use this package in academic field, please cite:
Wang, Shixiang, et al. &amp;quot;The predictive power of tumor mutational burden in lung cancer immunotherapy response is influenced by patients&amp;#39; sex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UCSCXenaTools: R API for UCSC Xena Hubs</title>
      <link>/en/tools/ucscxenatools-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/tools/ucscxenatools-api/</guid>
      <description>This vignette gives users the summary information of API functions provided by UCSCXenaTools for UCSC Xena.
Before using API, user should know some concepts about Xena elements. Following description is copied from xenaPython __init__.py.
 Data rows are associated with “sample” IDs.
Sample IDs are unique within a “cohort”. s A “dataset” is a particular assay of a cohort, e.g. gene expression.
Datasets have associated metadata, specifying their data type and cohort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obtain RNAseq Values for a Specific Gene in Xena Database</title>
      <link>/en/post/2020-07-22-ucscxenatools-single-gene/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/2020-07-22-ucscxenatools-single-gene/</guid>
      <description>When using UCSCXenaTools package, you may want to focus on single gene analysis, a typical case has been shown in my previous blog UCSCXenaTools: Retrieve Gene Expression and Clinical Information from UCSC Xena for Survival Analysis. Here I will describe how to get single gene values (especially RNAseq data) in details. Let’s load package. library(UCSCXenaTools) #&amp;gt; ========================================================================================= #&amp;gt; UCSCXenaTools version 1.3.3 #&amp;gt; Project URL: https://github.com/ropensci/UCSCXenaTools #&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UCSCXenaTools: Retrieve Gene Expression and Clinical Information from UCSC Xena for Survival Analysis</title>
      <link>/en/post/ucscxenatools-201908/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/ucscxenatools-201908/</guid>
      <description>I thank the edition made by Stefanie Butland.
 The UCSC Xena platform provides an unprecedented resource for public omics data from big projects like The Cancer Genome Atlas (TCGA), however, it is hard for users to incorporate multiple datasets or data types, integrate the selected data with popular analysis tools or homebrewed code, and reproduce analysis procedures. To address this issue, we developed an R package UCSCXenaTools for enabling data retrieval, analysis integration and reproducible research for omics data from the UCSC Xena platform1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>