<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English blog on Shixiang Wang | 王诗翔</title>
    <link>/en/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English blog on Shixiang Wang | 王诗翔</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>UCSCXenaTools: Retrieve Gene Expression and Clinical Information from UCSC Xena for Survival Analysis</title>
      <link>/en/post/ucscxenatools-201908/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/ucscxenatools-201908/</guid>
      <description>In this technote I will outline how to use UCSCXenaTools package to pull gene expression and clinical data from UCSC Xena for survival analysis.
For general usage of UCSCXenaTools, please refer to package vignette. Any bug or feature request can be reported in GitHub issues.
Installation UCSCXenaTools is available from CRAN:
install.packages(&amp;quot;UCSCXenaTools&amp;quot;) Alternatively, the latest development version can be downloaded from GitHub:
remotes::install_github(&amp;quot;ropensci/UCSCXenaTools&amp;quot;, build_vignettes = TRUE, dependencies = TRUE)  How it works Before actually pulling data, understand how UCSCXenaTools 1 works (see Figure 1) will help user locate the most important function to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create logo for R package UCSCXenaTools with hexSticker</title>
      <link>/en/post/2019-06-20-how-i-create-ucscxenatools-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/2019-06-20-how-i-create-ucscxenatools-logo/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago, I asked Tyler about how did he create the logo of R package exoplanets. Figure 1: logo of R package exoplanets I really love this logo because it is very simple and elegant. He told me he used a software called omnigraffle to make the logos. I tried learning this software and still did not know how to use it to create a nice logo because</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balderdash</title>
      <link>/en/post/2019-06-05-balderdash/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/2019-06-05-balderdash/</guid>
      <description>2019-06-05 Learning programming languages after serveral years, it suddenly dawned on me that they are just tools we express our ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>